{
  "quiz_name": "Adobe Analytics Business Practitioner",
  "topics" :[
    {"key": "Business Analysis", "percent":  25},
    {"key": "Reporting and Dashboarding for Projects", "percent":  25}, 
    {"key": "Segmentation and Calculated Metrics", "percent": 25}, 
    {"key": "General tool knowledge and troubleshooting", "percent":  15 } ,
    {"key": "Administration", "percent":  10 }
  ],
  "percentageCorrectForPassingScore": 68, 
  "quiz_questions": [
    {
      "question_type":"Select the correct option.","question_text":"What is one method for providing more personalized viewer experiences? ","presented_options":["Restricting media scaling to Android users","Integrating third-party data sources with an organization's web analytics","Randomized ad serving","Removing social data from audience profiles"],"correct_options":["Integrating third-party data sources with an organization's web analytics"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":" Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"The reports and analytics capability provides which of the following benefits to users?","presented_options":["All available marketing data accessible in a single place","A variety of reports, but only in PDF format","Customizable dashboards to discover and share insights","Flexible digital asset management capabilities"],"correct_options":["All available marketing data accessible in a single place","Customizable dashboards to discover and share insights"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the four correct answers. ","question_text":"In addition to the reports and analytics, ad hoc analysis, and data workbench capabilities, what capabilities of Adobe Analytics did we discuss in this module? ","presented_options":["Experience Manager Assets","Data connectors","Test and Target","Digital Asset management","Report builder","Data warehouse","Dynamic tag management"],"correct_options":["Data connectors","Report builder","Data warehouse","Dynamic tag management"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Recent trends have led to the growing need for a marketing analytics solution that enables data-driven decision-making and personalized experiences Which of the following demonstrates the need for the Adobe Analytics solution? ","presented_options":["The recent dominance of a single mobile operating system.","The growing number and types of business intelligence.","The standardization of video delivery platforms.","The growing popularity of stationary and printed paper","The expectation of a consistent experience across channels."],"correct_options":["The growing number and types of business intelligence. ","The expectation of a consistent experience across channels."],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The Adobe Analytics solution is only available as a single package, so all customers receive the exact same level of service. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Digital marketing analysts need to know how visitors use each channel, which campaigns are effective, and how tot harmonize their efforts. Before they can do any of these activities, what must they first be able to do? ","presented_options":["Build comprehensive audience profiles","Create engagement scores","Dynamically scale video to specific devices","Make sense of data scattered across organizations"],"correct_options":["Make sense of data scattered across organizations"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The data workbench capability combines terabytes of online and offline data sources to enable the statistically valid audience segments, engagement scores, and conversion data. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The growing number and types of marketing data make it difficult to discover the insights needed to drive personalized experiences and make data-driven decisions. What org tendency amplifies this obstacle? ","presented_options":["Structuring teams around a single area of focus","Hiring marketers based on Linkedin profiles","Restricting collaboration to email-only discussions","Poor security and privacy policies"],"correct_options":["Structuring teams around a single area of focus"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The ad hoc analysis capability enables marketers to quickly identify their high value audience profiles by doing which of the following? ","presented_options":["Subscribe to their twitter accounts","Explore real time visitor data to build segments","Suggest industry standard ad blocking software","Send unsolicited email promotions"],"correct_options":["Explore real time visitor data to build segments"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"Adobe analytics brings together data from online and offline marketing channels to reveal hidden patterns within Big Data. This combined view gives marketers real-time insights into campaign performance and cross-channel customer behavior. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["What is Adobe Analytics? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"With the ad hoc capability of adobe analytics, marketers can explore their marketing data in real time to create comprehensive views of high value visitor segments. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Ad Hoc Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The ad hoc capability enables marketers to do which of the following? ","presented_options":["Identify each visitor's annual salary","Know which visitors are the most valueable to their business","Provide each visitor with tax free consulations","Automatically segment visitors by blood type"],"correct_options":["Know which visitors are the most valueable to their business"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Ad Hoc Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What can marketers do with the ad hoc analysis capability's control over real time visitor data? ","presented_options":["Build high-value customer segments","Offer discounted licenses to Adobe creative cloud","Seamlessly integrate systems recently acquired from other companies","Understand how visitors interact with an organzation's site and digital assets"],"correct_options":["Build high-value customer segments","Understand how visitors interact with an organization's site and digital assets"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Ad Hoc Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are digital marketing business challenges that the ad hoc analysis capability of Adobe analytics was designed to address? ","presented_options":["Marketers struggle to understand the attributes and behavior of valuable visitors and customers","Reducing the company's ecological footprint by encouraging public transportation","Understanding how customers interact with a brand's digital properties and channels","Software constraints restrict the ability to answer new questions sparked by data","The inability to scale high definition video to mobile devices and channels"],"correct_options":["Marketers struggle to understand the attributes and behavior of valuable visitors and customers","Understanding how customers interact with a brand's digital properties and channels","Software constraints restrict the ability to answer new questions sparked by data"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Ad Hoc Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The ad hoc analysis capability enables multidimensional site analysis so marketers can determine the most popular, effective, and valuable engagement points with customers and prospects. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Ad Hoc Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How does the data connectors capability of adobe analytics allow marketers to break down data siloes to discover the best ways to invest marketing resources? ","presented_options":["It provides access to powerful hacking tools","It provides access to a robust collection of sales leads","It provides access to a repository of digital media assets","It provides access to a large ecosystem of partner applications"],"correct_options":["It provides access to a large ecosystem of partner applications"],"exam_topics":["What are data connectors? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which capability of the adobe analytics solution enables organizations to combine marketing data from third party sources in order to gain a complete understanding of how visitors interact with digital properties? ","presented_options":["Data connectors","Activity Map","Dynamic tag","Report builder","Data warehouse"],"correct_options":["Data connectors"],"exam_topics":["What are data connectors? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following business intelligence challenges can be overcome using the data connectors capability of adobe analytics? ","presented_options":["The difficulty and expense of integrating marketing systems","Relying on IT resources to build integrations between marketing systems","Moderating branded social communities","Dynamically scaling video assets for web, mobile, and tablet devices"],"correct_options":["The difficulty and expense of integrating marketing systems","Relying on IT resources to build integrations between marketing systems"],"exam_topics":["What are data connectors? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"Using the data connectors capability to create only a single connection between email and web analytics is not likely to produce a higher resolution, cross channel view of visitors than previous to the connection. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["What are data connectors? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The data connectors capability provides purpose built connectors for simple integration of adobe analytics with a broad ecosystem of third party marketing applications. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["What are data connectors? "],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The reports and analytics capability comes with all implementations of adobe analytics, but does not integrate with the other solutions of the marketing cloud. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics: Starting points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The marketing reports and analytics capability provides marketers interactive dashboards for accurate visual analyses and attribution of campaign data. As discussed in this module, what benefit does this feature provide? ","presented_options":["It makes the work day more engaging","It increases bandwidth for video streams","It deletes visitor data after collection to ensure privacy"],"correct_options":["It makes big data's insights accessible and actionable for marketers"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics: Starting points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are business challenges marketers face that can be addressed by the reports and analytics capability of adobe analytics? ","presented_options":["An overreliance on paper products","A surplus of employees","Inflexible reporting tools that restrict easy sharing of insights","Data is siloed across the organization","Lax privacy protection of customer data"],"correct_options":["Inflexible reporting tools that restrict easy sharing of insights","Data is siloed across the organization"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics: Starting points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are features enabled by the reports and analytics capability of Adobe analytics? ","presented_options":["Communicate insights to stakeholders with robust reports and dashboards","Easily create customized dashboards to explore data and discover insights","Scale video dynamically across devices","Authenticate users to stream video content directly to their tablet devices","Enable create once, deploy everywhere strategies for social campaigns"],"correct_options":["Communicate insights to stakeholders with robust reports and dashboards","Easily create customized dashboards to explore data and discover insights","See and access marketing data from all campaigns in a single place"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics: Starting points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The reports and analytics capability collects all of an organizations data into one place, providing marketers a more comprehensive view of their visitors and campaign performance. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics: Starting points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The report builder capability of adobe analytics combines real time data from adobe analytics with the ubiquity of microsoft excel so marketers can easily create, customize, edit, and distribute reports. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Report Builder"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The report builder capability combines real time data from adobe analytics with which application? ","presented_options":["Apple keynote","Google analytics","Amazon kindle fire","Microsoft excel"],"correct_options":["Microsoft excel"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Report Builder"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What kind of actions can users perform with the custom dashboards enabled by the report builder of adobe analytics? ","presented_options":["Data mash-ups","Unlimited segmentation of customer data","Quick analysis of adobe analytics data","Request approval from stakeholders for a greater marketing budget"],"correct_options":["Data mash-ups","Quick analysis of adobe analytics data"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Report Builder"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What business challenges do marketers face that the report builder capability of adobe analytics can help them address? ","presented_options":["Additional and custom analysis on adobe analytics data","Spam filters for email applications","Secure DRM for streaming video media","Familiar tools for easily exploration and sharing of data"],"correct_options":["Additional and custom analysis on adobe analytics data","Familiar tools for easily exploration and sharing of data"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Report Builder"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The report builder capability only comes with implementations of adobe analytics premium. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["What is Analytics?: Report Builder"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What business challenges do marketers face that the dynamic tag management capability of Adobe Analytics can help address?","presented_options":["Management of complex form based interactions","Dozens of tags from different applications complicates collection and management","Marketer reliance on IT","Proliferation of spam on branded social communities"],"correct_options":["Dozens of tags from different applications complicates collection and management","Marketer reliance on IT"],"exam_topics":["Dynamic Tag Management: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The dynamic tag management capability of Adobe Analytics enables marketers to precisely and easily define what types of data and events they want to collect using rules-driven tag execution.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Dynamic Tag Management: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"With the robust and intuitive interface of the dynamic tag management capability of Adobe Analytics, marketers can easily deploy data collection for what purposes?","presented_options":["Organize business specific marketing data","Conceal business specific marketing data","Distribute business specific marketing data","Eliminate business specific marketing data"],"correct_options":["Organize business specific marketing data","Distribute business specific marketing data"],"exam_topics":["Dynamic Tag Management: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The dynamic tag management capability of the Adobe Analytics solution is available to Adobe Marketing Cloud customers at no additional cost.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Dynamic Tag Management: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"With what feature of the dynamic tag management capability of Adobe Analytics can marketers define what data they want to collect and how it will be distributed?","presented_options":["Rules driven tag execution","Unlimited segmentation","Importing adobe analytics data into excel dashboards","Multidimensional site analysis"],"correct_options":["Rules driven tag execution"],"exam_topics":["Dynamic Tag Management: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What can marketers do by combining online and offline data sources with the data workbench capability of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["Refine customer profiles","Direct the right content on the right channel at the right time","Reduce buffering of online video platforms","Moderate branded social communities"],"correct_options":["Refine customer profiles","Direct the right content on the right channel at the right time"],"exam_topics":["Data Workbench: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"The data workbench capability of Adobe Analytics combines all of an organizations data into one place for a detailed view of their customers, enabling marketers to do which of the following?","presented_options":["Eliminate duplication of digital assets","Predict the success of campaigns","Test offer and content combinations for different visitor segments","Maximize the impact of ad spend"],"correct_options":["Predict the success of campaigns","Maximize the impact of ad spend"],"exam_topics":["Data Workbench: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of an organizations data can be gathered by the data workbench capability of Adobe Analytics for a comprehensive, 360 view of customers?","presented_options":["Online data","Third party data","Employee payroll data","Internal HR data","Offline data"],"correct_options":["Online data","Third party data","Offline data"],"exam_topics":["Data Workbench: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The data workbench capability gives marketers predictive capabilities to measure likely customer responses to new efforts.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Data Workbench: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The data workbench capability combines all of an organizations multi-channel data with offline customer interactions for the control and insight marketers need to optimize their marketing campaigns.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Data Workbench: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are marketing challenges that the data warehouse capability of Adobe Analytics can help organizations to overcome?","presented_options":["Identifying smaller opportunities within deep product catalogs","Recruting MBA grads for marketing positions","Moderating branded social communities","Reprocessing reports with new or updated information"],"correct_options":["Identifying smaller opportunities within deep product catalogs","Reprocessing reports with new or updated information"],"exam_topics":["Data Warehouse: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"Organizations can use the data warehouse capability of Adobe Analytics to store and back-up their hit-level data, but they are not able to query or run reports on that data.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Data Warehouse: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The data warehouse capability of Adobe Analytics automates reports on what kinds of data?","presented_options":["Monthly usage of mobile apps","Demographic data from government census","Granular level marketing data","Payroll data"],"correct_options":["Granular level marketing data"],"exam_topics":["Data Warehouse: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The data warehouse capability of Adobe Analytics is a repository for granular-level marketing data.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Data Warehouse: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The data warehouse capability offers the functionality to re-process months and even years of an organizations raw historical data. This feature provides what benefit to marketers?","presented_options":["Creating dedicated branded social communities","Updated information to determine the effect of ongoing marketing campaigns","Eliminate duplication of digital assets","Integrating user-generated content into owned properties"],"correct_options":["Updated information to determine the effect of ongoing marketing campaigns"],"exam_topics":["Data Warehouse: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following best describes the Analysis Workspace capability of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["It helps the user understand individuals who reside in multiple audience segments","It identifies anomalous behaviors that don't match the user's forecasting expectations","It provides the clearest picture of a mobile app's performance","It empowers the user to utilize analytics and improve decision making","It identifies the most valuable elements of individual web pages and digital properties"],"correct_options":["It empowers the user to utilize analytics and improve decision making"],"exam_topics":["Analysis Workspace: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following tools is not provided in the Analysis Workspace of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["Cohort analysis","Pathing","Segmentation","Attribution","Freeform tables"],"correct_options":["Segmentation"],"exam_topics":["Analysis Workspace: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Analysis Workspace enables business users and data scientists to perform which one of the following?","presented_options":["Fine-tune their digital properties to drive the right message to the right audience","Build reusable projects customized to role-based workflows","Identify the hidden patterns and contributing factors for statistical anomalies","Identify overlaps between audience types","Create marketing campaign links to their apps in the apple store or google play"],"correct_options":["Build reusable projects customized to role-based workflows"],"exam_topics":["Analysis Workspace: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following statements about the Analysis Workspace capability of Adobe Analytics is true?","presented_options":["It comes with most of the implementations of adobe analytics","It enables business users to explore their visitor data in real time","It is accessible only to specially trained data analysts","It provides insights limited only to the individual who discovers them"],"correct_options":["It enables business users to explore their visitor data in real time"],"exam_topics":["Analysis Workspace: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Analysis Workspace was built for which of the following?","presented_options":["Comsumption","Location","Conversion","Speed","Collaboration"],"correct_options":["Speed","Collaboration"],"exam_topics":["Analysis Workspace: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following statements about the Activity Map capability of Adobe Analytics are true?","presented_options":["It presents just an aggregated view of everyone who has visited the page","It overlays important information directly on the webpage or digital property","It can break out results based on audience segments","It comes with most of the implementations of adobe analytics"],"correct_options":["It overlays important information directly on the webpage or digital property","It can break out results based on audience segments"],"exam_topics":["Activity Map: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Activity Map enables users to perform which of the following?","presented_options":["Create marketing campaign links to their apps","Build reusable projects customized to role-based workflows","Identify the hidden patterns and contributing factors for statistical anomalies","Fine tune their digital properties to drive the right message to the right audience","Identify overlaps between audience types"],"correct_options":["Fine tune their digital properties to drive the right message to the right audience"],"exam_topics":["Activity Map: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The Activity Map capability of Adobe Analytics enables analysts and business users to easily view traffic, conversion, and success metrics for individual page elements. Which of these is not a page element Activity Map monitors?","presented_options":["Buttons","Pathing","Banners","Advertisments","Hotspots"],"correct_options":["Pathing"],"exam_topics":["Activity Map: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following problems are addressed by the Activity Map capability of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["Many teams has difficulty sharing projects with other members of the organization","It is difficult to analyze behaviors that don't match a user's forecasting expectations","Visitors respond differently to various page elements, depending on who they are","Most organizations lack tools that enable them to view customer data as it happens"],"correct_options":["Visitors respond differently to various page elements, depending on who they are","Most organizations lack tools that enable them to view customer data as it happens"],"exam_topics":["Activity Map: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following best describes the Activity Map capability of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["It helps the user understand individuals who reside in multiple audience segments","It empowers the user to utilize analytics and improve decision making","It provides the clearest picture of a mobile app's performance","It identifies the most valuable elements of individual web pages and digital properties","It identifies anomalous behaviors that don't match the user's forecasting expectations"],"correct_options":["It identifies the most valuable elements of individual web pages and digital properties"],"exam_topics":["Activity Map: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following statements about the Anomaly Detection capability of Adobe Analytics is true?","presented_options":["It helps determine why a data anomaly occurred","It uncovers anomalous behaviors or patterns that would have otherwise gone unnoticed","It saves countless hours searching for reasons why company metrics may have changed","It comes with most of the implementations of adobe analytics"],"correct_options":["It uncovers anomalous behaviors or patterns that would have otherwise gone unnoticed"],"exam_topics":["Anomaly Detection & Contribution Analysis: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"In terms of data anomalies, Anomaly Detection determines the what, and then Contribution Analysis determines the ________.","presented_options":["Who","How","Where","Why"],"correct_options":["Why"],"exam_topics":["Anomaly Detection & Contribution Analysis: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following best describes the Anomaly Detection and Contribution Analysis capabilities of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["It empowers the user to utilize analytics and improve decision making","It identifies anomalous behaviors that don't match the user's forecasting expectations","It helps the user understand individuals who reside in multiple audience segments","It identifies the most valuable elements of individual web pages and digital properties","It provides the clearest picture of the user's mobile app's performance"],"correct_options":["It identifies anomalous behaviors that don't match the user's forecasting expectations"],"exam_topics":["Anomaly Detection & Contribution Analysis: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Anomaly Detection and Contribution Analysis enables users to perform which of the following?","presented_options":["Fine-tune their digital properties to drive the right message to the right audience","Identify overlaps between audience types","Create marketing campaign links to their apps in the app store","Identify the hidden patterns and contributing factors for statistical anomalies","Build reusable projects customized to role-based workflows"],"correct_options":["Identify the hidden patterns and contributing factors for statistical anomalies"],"exam_topics":["Anomaly Detection & Contribution Analysis: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following statements about the Contribution Analysis capability of Adobe Analytics is true?","presented_options":["It identifies data that is out of the ordinary","It presents an aggregated view of everyone who has visited a page","It comes with most of the implementations of Adobe analytics","It identifies contributing factors for significant changes in trended data and anomalies"],"correct_options":["It identifies contributing factors for significant changes in trended data and anomalies"],"exam_topics":["Anomaly Detection & Contribution Analysis: Starting Points"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Through proper segmentation of their unique visitors, companies ______________.","presented_options":["Simplify the analysis of data by surfacing the most relevant trends","Improve the overall efficiency and relevance of their digital properties","Are able to queue up analytics data when visitors are offline","Save time, money, and resources"],"correct_options":["Improve the overall efficiency and relevance of their digital properties","Save time, money, and resources"],"exam_topics":["Segment IQ"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following best describes the Segment IQ capability of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["It provides the clearest picture of the user's mobile app's performance","It helps the user understand individuals who reside in multiple audience segments","It empowers the user to utilize analytics and improve decision making","It identifies the most valuable elements of individual web pages and digital properties","It identifies anomalous behaviors that don't match the user's forecasting expectations"],"correct_options":["It helps the user understand individuals who reside in multiple audience segments"],"exam_topics":["Segment IQ"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following statements is true?","presented_options":["Most audience members fit neatly into a single segment","Segment IQ compares audiences against visitors to similar websites of competitors","Segment IQ includes the latest in machine learning insight innovation","Finding and comparing minute patterns in behaviors using forms is an efficient analytics tool"],"correct_options":["Segment IQ includes the latest in machine learning insight innovation"],"exam_topics":["Segment IQ"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following statements about the Segment IQ capability of Adobe Analytics is true?","presented_options":["It identifies only the similarities in audience preferences","It identifies only the differences in audience preferences","It compares audiences against each other across all of a company's metrics","It comes with most of the implementations of adobe analytics"],"correct_options":["It compares audiences against each other across all of a company's metrics"],"exam_topics":["Segment IQ"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Segment IQ enables users to perform which of the following?","presented_options":["Identify overlaps between audience types","Fine-tune their digital properties to drive the right message to the right audience","Identify the hidden patterns and contributing factors for statistical anomalies","Create marketing campaign links to their apps in the app store","Build reusable projects customized to role-based workflows"],"correct_options":["Identify overlaps between audience types"],"exam_topics":["Segment IQ"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following statements about the Mobile Analytics capability of Adobe Analytics is false?","presented_options":["It enables companies to quickly implement capabilities like A/B testing and mobile targeting in their apps","It allows organizations to indirectly measure the effectiveness of their mobile app investment","It identifies which app features lead to repeat launches and in-app conversions","It enables the delivery of messaging and personalization based on the user's proximity to beacons"],"correct_options":["It allows organizations to indirectly measure the effectiveness of their mobile app investment"],"exam_topics":["What is analytics?: Mobile Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Mobile Analytics enables users to perform which of the following?","presented_options":["Build reusable projects customized to the role based workflows","Identify overlaps between audience types","Create marketing campaign links to their apps in the app store","Identify the hidden patterns and contributing factors for statistical anomalies","Fine-tune their digital properties to drive the rihgt message to the right audience"],"correct_options":["Create marketing campaign links to their apps in the app store"],"exam_topics":["What is analytics?: Mobile Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following best describes the Mobile Analytics capability of Adobe Analytics?","presented_options":["It provides the clearest picture of the user's mobile app's performance","It identifies the most valuable elements of individual web pages and digital properties","It empowers the user to utilize analytics and improve decision making","It helps the user understand individuals who reside in multiple audience segments","It identifies anomalous behaviors that don't match the user's forecasting expectations"],"correct_options":["It provides the clearest picture of the user's mobile app's performance"],"exam_topics":["What is analytics?: Mobile Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Using Mobile Analytics, companies can measure usage behavior patterns based on _______?","presented_options":["Consumption","Location","Collaboration","Speed","Conversion"],"correct_options":["Location"],"exam_topics":["What is analytics?: Mobile Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Using Mobile Analytics, when can companies segment customers based on their utilization of the app?","presented_options":["When the customer appears in two or more segments","When the customer downloads the app","When the customer first launches the app","When the customer interacts with two or more elements in the app"],"correct_options":["When the customer first launches the app"],"exam_topics":["What is analytics?: Mobile Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 1","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following functions can you perform using web analytics?","presented_options":["Optimizing websites","Increasing conversion through optimization of websites or marketing to websites","Optimizing products through extensive market research","Optimizing search engines","Optimizing marketing to websites"],"correct_options":["Optimizing websites","Increasing conversion through optimization of websites or marketing to websites","Optimizing marketing to websites"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Consider a scenario where you own an online retail clothing store. How can you use Adobe Analytics to help you in the different aspects of your business?","presented_options":["You can use it to maintain a record of your total sales, profit, and losses","It can help you shape your customer interactions and future marketing efforts to drive more conversions","It can help you set up your store to better cater to your customer's needs","It can help you undestand your customer's behaviors, including their movements, website activity, preferences, and purchases","You can derive a deeper understanding of your product specifications"],"correct_options":["It can help you shape your customer interactions and future marketing efforts to drive more conversions","It can help you understand your customer's behaviors, including their movements, website activity, preferences, and purchases","You can use it to maintain a record of your total sales, profit, and losses"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How does a great web analyst drive action with their managers or stakeholders?","presented_options":["By providing recommended website or marketing changes based on their analysis","By talking in terms of web servers and web models","By analyzing and providing reports about senior management efficiency","By using terms that are understood in the business context and that highlight the revenue"],"correct_options":["By providing recommended website or marketing changes based on their analysis"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the goal of a web analyst?","presented_options":["To analyze data and provide insights to stakeholders","To analyze and maintain web development cost","To develop knowledge about the techniques and principals of internet development","To move from data to insight and then to action"],"correct_options":["To move from data to insight and then to action"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following activities help improve economic value for your client?","presented_options":["Continually running and modifying reports to ensure that stakeholders receive the best reports","Reviewing the four phases of customer conversion for opportunities of improvement","Performing A/B and multivariate testing for ongoing testing","Using the web analytics process to continuously re-evaluate your goals and KPIs","Recommending enhancements that will expand the scope and depth of the implementation"],"correct_options":["Reviewing the four phases of customer conversion for opportunities of improvement","Performing A/B and multivariate testing for ongoing testing","Using the web analytics process to continuously re-evaluate your goals and KPIs"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the goal of acquisition in customer conversion?","presented_options":["Understanding how to reduce attrition and maximize the number of conversions","Understanding the visitor's value","Understanding which content is influencing and driving website conversions","Understanding where visitors come from"],"correct_options":["Understanding where visitors come from"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following best practices should you use when analyzing data as part of the web analytics process?","presented_options":["Evaluating the website and the marketing performance toward the website","Generating reports based on the KPI data","Creating reports that allow you to identify patterns and anomalies","Extracting the detail requirements from goals for tracking specific web and marketing initiatives","Using data to hypothesize areas and opportunities within the website that can be improved and exploited"],"correct_options":["Evaluating the website and the marketing performance toward the website","Creating reports that allow you to identify patterns and anomalies","Using data to hypothesize areas and opportunities within the website that can be improved and exploited"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following responsibilities are performed by a great analyst?","presented_options":["Implementing changes in products sold on stakeholder websites","Improving website navigation, aesthetics, content, and website conversion","Recommending website or marketing changes based on their own analysis","Learning from past marketing efforts to improve future campaigns that increase conversion","Recommending changes in software tools"],"correct_options":["Improving website navigation, aesthetics, content, and website conversion","Recommending website or marketing changes based on their own analysis","Learning from past marketing efforts to improve future campaigns that increase conversion"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What is the importance of governance within the web analytics process?","presented_options":["It allows you to automate report distribution","It ensures that your measurement strategy is aligned to your business goals","It assists in implementation architecture","It allows you to understand and work toward what is most important for the company as it evolves over time"],"correct_options":["It ensures that your measurement strategy is aligned to your business goals","It allows you to understand and work toward what is most important for the company as it evolves over time"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following factors prevent actionable analytics?","presented_options":["Following the web analytics process for continuous improvement","Performing A/B and multivariate test for ongoing testing","Performing the reporting process and not getting to the ROI","Measuring interesting data and not actionable insights","Implementing endless enhancements and additional requirements without tracking"],"correct_options":["Performing the reporting process and not getting to the ROI","Measuring interesting data and not actionable insights","Implementing endless enhancements and additional requirements without tracking"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the goal of the second step in the web analytics process? ","presented_options":["Defining organzational goals and KPIs","Optimizing performance through experimentation and testing","Analyzing data effectively to deliver actionable insights","Reporting effectively to answer specific questions that your stakeholders have"],"correct_options":["Reporting effectively to answer specific questions that your stakeholders have"],"exam_topics":["Introduction to Web Analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following do you need to create a Solution Design Reference (SDR) document?","presented_options":["Data from website testing","KPIs","Historical data of the company","Key business requirements"],"correct_options":["KPIs","Key business requirements"],"exam_topics":["Designing and documenting the solution design reference"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are characteristics of a good Solution Design Reference (SDR) document?","presented_options":["It is scalable and efficient","It is based on a set of established global standards","It provides information about customers","It answers critical business questions","It's maintained by adobe client care"],"correct_options":["It is scalable and efficient","It is based on a set of established global standards","It answers critical business questions"],"exam_topics":["Designing and documenting the solution design reference"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What are the key elements to include in the Solution Design Reference (SDR)?","presented_options":["All the client's KPIs","All adobe analytics variables features and functions mapping to the KBRs","All marketing and sales reports","All the client's business goals and objectives"],"correct_options":["All adobe analytics variables features and functions mapping to the KBRs"],"exam_topics":["Designing and documenting the solution design reference"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"It is important that you use a Solution Design Reference (SDR) template so that your SDR is consistent for all Adobe clients.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Designing and documenting the solution design reference"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"You should focus on only three to five key business requirements (KBRs) when developing the solution design.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Designing and documenting the solution design reference"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"Increase in online sales is an example of a key performance indicator (KPI)","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Consider a scenario where you have to gather requirements for your clients firm, a medium-sized retail business. Which of the following roles should be the highest role you interact with to understand your clients overall corporate goals?","presented_options":["Internet executives","CEO","CFO","Internet specialists"],"correct_options":["CFO"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Consider a scenario where your client has a company-wide goal to improve sales, and has set goals and objectives across the different levels of key business requirements (KBRs) to achieve this goal. Which of the following are examples of an online initiative to support this goal?","presented_options":["Creating engagement metrics, to combine product views, searches, and store locator usage","Expanding the product line","Reducing shopping cart abandonment","Improving website search"],"correct_options":["Reducing shopping cart abandonment","Improving website search"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is a key performance indicator (KPI)?","presented_options":["A set of solutions that contains changes made to the current state of an organization","A metric for measuring the success or failure toward reaching your goal","A goal or an objective that is critical for the success of your client's business","A document that details the business solution for a project"],"correct_options":["A metric for measuring the success or failure toward reaching your goal"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is an online key business requirement (KBR)?","presented_options":["Online tasks that support online goals and initiatives","Strategic online initiatives to achieve online goals","Strategic online business goals or objectives","Strategic company wide business goals or objectives"],"correct_options":["Strategic online business goals or objectives"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Consider a scenario where you need to interview stakeholders about their companys websites, where websites are not the company's primary source of income. Which of the following questions would you ask your stakeholders about their websites?","presented_options":["Why does your website exist?","Does your website have a clear call to action on each web page?","Does your website contain a website map that is easily accessible?","How does your website contribute to your organizational goals?","How does your website make money?"],"correct_options":["Why does your website exist? ","How does your website contribute to your organizational goals?","How does your website make money?"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following questions should you ask when interviewing executives at your clients organization?","presented_options":["Why are you trying to increase sales?","Who is your typical user or customer?","How does your business make money?","What are your organization's main goals?","What are the main areas of focus for your organization?"],"correct_options":["How does your business make money?","What are your organization's main goals?","What are the main areas of focus for your organization?"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following sources of information would you refer to for gathering client requirements?","presented_options":["Historical data of the company","Industry or product fundamentals","Interviews of executives and key stakeholder that cover their business goals","Online discussion forums","A client requirements document created previously"],"correct_options":["Industry or product fundamentals","Interviews of executives and key stakeholder that cover their business goals","A client requirements document created previously"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following best practices should you follow when defining organizational goals and key performance indicators (KPIs)?","presented_options":["Assisting in drafting the analytics solution to make it uniquely tailored to the organization","Making changes to the website and testing its effectiveness","Extracting the detail requirements for tracking specific web and marketing initiatives","Interviewing the the organzation's key stakeholders by roles that can define goals and KPIs","Taking baseline measurement of goals"],"correct_options":["Extracting the detail requirements for tracking specific web and marketing initiatives","Interviewing the the organzation's key stakeholders by roles that can define goals and KPIs","Assisting in drafting the analytics solution to make it uniquely tailored to the organization"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following levels of key business requirements (KBRs) should you focus on when providing an Adobe Analytics solution for your clients?","presented_options":["Enterprise KBR at the CEO level","Online initiatives to achieve online goals","Online KBRs consisting of online goals and objectives","Online tactical business requirements consisting of tasks to achieve online goals"],"correct_options":["Online initiatives to achieve online goals","Online KBRs consisting of online goals and objectives"],"exam_topics":["Forming Business Requirements"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 2","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What contextual data reports can you access in Activity Map?","presented_options":["Ranked metrics report","Links on page report","Page details report","Page path report"],"correct_options":["Links on page report","Page details report"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"If you are looking at a Page Views report as opposed to an eVar report, then what format is the report in?","presented_options":["Normal","Ranked","Trended","Gantt"],"correct_options":["Trended"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"You are tracking Username in prop17 to use for Classifications later. How would you navigate to that report, with a standard menu structure?","presented_options":["View all reports, custom traffic, username","View all reports, custom conversion, custom conversion 11-20, username","View all reports, custom traffic, custom traffic 11-20, username","View all reports, custom traffic 11-20, username"],"correct_options":["View all reports, custom traffic, custom traffic 11-20, username"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"In which of the following reports do you use the metric click-throughs?","presented_options":["Custom links","Pages","Tracking codes","eVars"],"correct_options":["Tracking codes"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What features are available only in the primary dimension reportlet?","presented_options":["Losers","Search filter","Detail view","Gainers","Most popular"],"correct_options":["Search filter","Detail view"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following reports give you information about how visitors arrive at your site?","presented_options":["Marketing channels","Pages","Tracking code","Internal URL","Traffic sources"],"correct_options":["Marketing channels","Tracking code","Traffic sources"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is important to remember about choosing metrics and dimensions for your real-time reports?","presented_options":["They all must be persistent variables","They all must be events","They all must be standard variables, not custom","they all must in the same beacon"],"correct_options":["they all must in the same beacon"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"If you want to look at a pages report for the last month by popularity, which type of report should you run?","presented_options":["Gantt","Trended","Normal","Ranked"],"correct_options":["Ranked"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What are the two modes available in Activity Map? ","presented_options":["Standard","Real-time","Historical","Live"],"correct_options":["Standard","Live"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What does the Admin need to do to ensure that Activity Map is set up?","presented_options":["Follow the instructions on the report suite setting page of the admin console","Set up the customer segments in the segment manager","Update the s_code file to H27.6 or later","Update AppMeasurement code to 1.6 or later"],"correct_options":["Follow the instructions on the report suite setting page of the admin console","Update AppMeasurement code to 1.6 or later"],"exam_topics":["Interface Overview"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the definition of a click-through?","presented_options":["It's what occurs when a visitor accesses a page on your website","The number of times that a tracking code for a given campaign was passed into reporting","It's what occurs when a visitor accesses a page on your website","The number of times that a value was set for a variable"],"correct_options":["The number of times that a tracking code for a given campaign was passed into reporting"],"exam_topics":["Metrics V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is a calculated metric?","presented_options":["A standard metric available by default in the metrics menu","One of 1000 custom success events","A custom metric that is created from exisiting metrics","An algorithm used to generate reports in reports & analytics"],"correct_options":["A custom metric that is created from exisiting metrics"],"exam_topics":["Metrics V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Your site has several custom links. Which of the following is a true statement of what you can expect when viewing a Traffic Variable report?","presented_options":["There is no way to know for sure without knowing the specific variable settings","Page views will be higher than instances","Instances will be higher than page views","Page views and instances will be equal"],"correct_options":["Instances will be higher than page views"],"exam_topics":["Metrics V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are standard metrics?","presented_options":["Purchase","Event1","Sign-ups","Page view","prodView"],"correct_options":["Purchase","Page view","prodView"],"exam_topics":["Metrics V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the purpose of a participation metric?","presented_options":["To assign linear credit to success events to all values of an eVar that were passed during a visit","To expire the metric after the eVar has been stored for a set time","To give first allocation to metrics for prop values passed during a visit","To assign full credit from success evcents to all values of a data dimension that were passed during a visit"],"correct_options":["To assign full credit from success evcents to all values of a data dimension that were passed during a visit"],"exam_topics":["Metrics V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following components can you use when creating a segment?","presented_options":["Alerts","Targets","Segments","Metrics","Dimensions"],"correct_options":["Segments","Metrics","Dimensions"],"exam_topics":["Segmentation V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"When you create a virtual report suite, what does it inherit from the parent report suite?","presented_options":["The personal bookmarks and component settings are the same","All data is the same, but the variables and settings are different","The group permissions and marketing cloud segments are the same","All variable names and admin settins are the same, only the data is different"],"correct_options":["All variable names and admin settins are the same, only the data is different"],"exam_topics":["Segmentation V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How do you add a segment to a report in Reports & Analytics?","presented_options":["Drag and drop the new segment onto the report","Click add segment and select the segment from the list","Select the segment from the drop down list","Click show segments, select the desired segment, and then click apply"],"correct_options":["Click show segments, select the desired segment, and then click apply"],"exam_topics":["Segmentation V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following operators do you use to build a sequential segment?","presented_options":["And","Then","Or","Time"],"correct_options":["Then"],"exam_topics":["Segmentation V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"What do Virtual Report Suites do?","presented_options":["Improve security by controlling data that teams can view","Improve data aggregation by consolidating data into one report suite","Simplify group settings by merging all user management into a global report suite","Simplify implementation by segmenting data directly in the reports and analytics interface","Present only relevant data to each team"],"correct_options":["Improve security by controlling data that teams can view","Simplify implementation by segmenting data directly in the reports and analytics interface","Present only relevant data to each team"],"exam_topics":["Segmentation V2"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the main purpose of Contribution Analysis?","presented_options":["To analyze the participation of metrics for a specific eVar report","To leverage multiple segments to analyze a report","To identify contributing factors of a metric anomaly","To compare the contribution of metrics toward conversion across different data dimensions"],"correct_options":["To identify contributing factors of a metric anomaly"],"exam_topics":["Contribution Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What does a Contribution Score of <-1> indicate about the selected item compared to its normal behavior?","presented_options":["Insignificant statistical value","No special differences","Complete inverse association","Strong distinction from the norm"],"correct_options":["Complete inverse association"],"exam_topics":["Contribution Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"By applying advanced statistics, what is Contribution Analysis able to do?","presented_options":["Offer solutions to anomalies based on customer interests","Plot future growth from concurrent trends","Display all relevant factors visually","Identify an emerging trend across a given time period","Learn patterns inherent in the data"],"correct_options":["Display all relevant factors visually","Identify an emerging trend across a given time period","Learn patterns inherent in the data"],"exam_topics":["Contribution Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"he tree graph found in the Contribution Drill-down section is used to represent pre-built segments, or ones you build yourself.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Contribution Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Where do you access the Contribution Analysis report?","presented_options":["From the anomaly detection report analysis queue","From the manage contribution analysis submenu in the view all reports menu","From the manage contribution analysis link in the components menu","From the more options menu at the top of any report"],"correct_options":["From the anomaly detection report analysis queue"],"exam_topics":["Contribution Analysis"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 3","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"Adobe recommends maintaining one JavaScript file even when you need to have multiple report suites.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the name of the Global JavaScript file?","presented_options":["eVar.js file","campaign.js file","products.js file","AppMeasurement.js file"],"correct_options":["AppMeasurement.js file"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the Adobe Debugger?","presented_options":["A tool used to read adobe analytics variables placed on the pages of a website","A tool used to build data values for adobe analytics","A tool used for data reporting and analytics","A toolused for sending image requests"],"correct_options":["A tool used to read adobe analytics variables placed on the pages of a website"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What options can you use for structuring a report suite architecture to provide both a global and a local view?","presented_options":["Global report suite with child report suite","Roll up report suite","One report suite for each website","Global report suite with virtual report suite"],"correct_options":["Global report suite with child report suite","Global report suite with virtual report suite"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"What are the criteria for measuring an ideal report suite architecture?","presented_options":["Data collection","eVar persistence","Global pathing","Global metrics","Visitor deduplication"],"correct_options":["eVar persistence","Global pathing","Visitor deduplication"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following parameters would be last in the web beacon query string?","presented_options":["t","ns","pageName","c","AQE","AQB"],"correct_options":["AQE"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What does the server do when it receives a web beacon image request?","presented_options":["Processes the name value pairs in the query string","Sends the requested image back to the browser","Converts the image request to data parameters and sends them back to the browser","Adds attributes directly to the AppMeasurement.js file"],"correct_options":["Processes the name value pairs in the query string","Sends the requested image back to the browser"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What represents over 95% of the elements in the Adobe Analytics web beacon? ","presented_options":["Query string parameters","Hit sources","Report suites","Cache busters","Data collection domains"],"correct_options":["Query string parameters"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Where can you locate the JavaScript code for installing the Adobe Debugger?","presented_options":["In the digital pulse debugger screenshot tool","Within the adobe knowledgebase plugin","In the help article, using the digitalpulse debugger","On the adobe debugger installation webpage"],"correct_options":["In the help article, using the digitalpulse debugger"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How does the Adobe Analytics web beacon image differ from just another image on the page?","presented_options":["It does not appear on the page","It is created through javascript in the getparameters.js file","It syncs with an automated ID","It adds attributes directly to the appmeasurement.js file"],"correct_options":["It does not appear on the page"],"exam_topics":["Reports and Analytics (R&A) Code"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the correct definition of configuration variables? ","presented_options":["Plug-ins that are used to run reports","Global variables that are accessed on every web page but need to be coded only once","Traffic variables that are used to retrieve analytics data","Variables that are used to read data from the web page"],"correct_options":["Global variables that are accessed on every web page but need to be coded only once"],"exam_topics":["Configuration and Automatic Variables"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Where would you place the Report Suite ID (RSID)?","presented_options":["In the s.currency variable","In the s.reportSuiteID variable","In the s.account variable","In the s.charSet variable"],"correct_options":["In the s.account variable"],"exam_topics":["Configuration and Automatic Variables"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which three types of links can be tracked using configuration variables? ","presented_options":["Download links","Entry links","Offline links","Exit links","Custom links"],"correct_options":["Download links","Exit links","Custom links"],"exam_topics":["Configuration and Automatic Variables"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Where do global variables exist in an Adobe Analytics implementation?","presented_options":["In the AppMeasurement.js global include file","in the eVars.js global include file","In the campaign.js global include file","In the products.js global include file"],"correct_options":["In the AppMeasurement.js global include file"],"exam_topics":["Configuration and Automatic Variables"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 4","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are functions of global variables?","presented_options":["Translating data into a different language","Capturing data in different languages","Converting currencies during online transactions","Tracking multiple websites or domains","Capturing customer movements, including mouse overs"],"correct_options":["Capturing data in different languages","Tracking multiple websites or domains","Converting currencies during online transactions"],"exam_topics":["Configuration and Automatic Variables"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the Adobe Analytics data types are text strings?","presented_options":["Metrics","Data dimensions","Data dimension elements","Numbers"],"correct_options":["Data dimensions","Data dimension elements"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"When determining a variable to use to answer business questions, it does not matter if you use a Traffic variable or a Conversion variable.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following are common examples of data collected from Conversion variables?","presented_options":["Page view, visit, visitor, and instance","Pages, site sections, and servers","Products, tracking codes, and internal search"],"correct_options":["Products, tracking codes, and internal search"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the first step to ensure that the Marketing Cloud IDs are mapping appropriately across solutions?","presented_options":["Clear cookies for your site to view the request to the marketing cloud id service","Use a packet analyzer in a web browser debugger to look for request going to dpm.demdex.net","Verify that the adobe analytics request contains a mid parameter or the marketing cloud ID"],"correct_options":["Clear cookies for your site to view the request to the marketing cloud id service"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are attributes of Traffic variables?","presented_options":["They are non persistent","Their values can change per image request","They are persistent","Their values are linked to user actions"],"correct_options":["They are non persistent","Their values can change per image request"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the Adobe Analytics data types are measurable actions?","presented_options":["Metrics","Data dimensions","Data elements","Text strings"],"correct_options":["Metrics"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Where in Adobe Analytics data flow do you apply Admin Tools settings to an image request?","presented_options":["Regional data collection servers","Regional data processing servers","Data warehouse","Query engine"],"correct_options":["Regional data processing servers"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Where is the first place that traffic and conversion variables data get stored and merged for queries?","presented_options":["RDC servers","RDP servers","Data warehouse","Query engine"],"correct_options":["Data warehouse"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the Adobe Analytics data types must be connected to another data type? ","presented_options":["Metrics","Data dimensions","Data collection domains","Reports","Caches"],"correct_options":["Data dimensions"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"True/False? ","question_text":"The purpose of Marketing Cloud ID Service is to create a universal identifier that visitors can use across all Adobe products.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Architecture and Data structure"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"In terms of reporting capability, how does the Hierarchy report differ from the Site Sections report?","presented_options":["Hierarchies can directly reflect product inventory; site sections cannot reflect product inventory","Hierarchies are linear; site sections are not","Hierarchies are vertical; site sections are horizontal"],"correct_options":["Hierarchies are vertical; site sections are horizontal"],"exam_topics":["Traffic variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Why is it important to have a good web page naming strategy?","presented_options":["Ensures that web page names are intuitive for analysts to understand","Prevents URLs from being submitted as the web page name","Guarantees a specific character count for web page names","Helps ensure success of a website","Ensures a specific location in the directory"],"correct_options":["Ensures that web page names are intuitive for analysts to understand","Prevents URLs from being substituted as the web page name","Helps ensure success of a website"],"exam_topics":["Traffic variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the function of Traffic Variables?","presented_options":["To collect traffic and pathing data to be displayed in R&A","To provide a global traffic and pathing view of multiple R&A suites","To build non-persistent web pages for clients websites in R&A","To automate the creation of custom insight variables for websites in R&A"],"correct_options":["To collect traffic and pathing data to be displayed in R&A"],"exam_topics":["Traffic variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the purpose of the s.channel variable?","presented_options":["Identifies content from different servers","Tracks website usage based on established content hierarchies","Identifies a website usage in a global environment","Identifies how various content categories are used by visitors"],"correct_options":["Identifies how various content categories are used by visitors"],"exam_topics":["Traffic variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What are the two common ways to name product detail web pages?","presented_options":["Using an aggregate or general page name","Using content hierarchy multi-level name","Using the full product name and the geographical area in which it is available","Using a unique product name"],"correct_options":["Using an aggregate or general page name","Using a unique product name"],"exam_topics":["Traffic variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are standard Retail success events?","presented_options":["Purchase","Application submission","Checkout","Product view","Internal campaign"],"correct_options":["Purchase","Checkout","Product view"],"exam_topics":["Success events & the product variable principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the definition of a conversion report?","presented_options":["Track the conversion of any type of reatil web site","Track pages relating to conversion transactions","Track the revenue,units, and orders of standard shopping cart web sites","Track visitor success or conversion of any events that occur on a web site"],"correct_options":["Track visitor success or conversion of any events that occur on a web site"],"exam_topics":["Success events & the product variable principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Conversion variables are commonly used for which of the following?","presented_options":["Product views","Campaign/promotion tracking","Internal search terms","A/B testing","Numbered range lists"],"correct_options":["Campaign/promotion tracking","Internal search terms","A/B testing"],"exam_topics":["Success events & the product variable principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are examples of custom events?","presented_options":["Checkout","Lead form completions","Product view","Subscriptions","Purchase"],"correct_options":["Lead form completions","Subscriptions"],"exam_topics":["Success events & the product variable principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the delimiter between product fields in the product string?","presented_options":["A semi-colon","A colon","A comma","A pipe"],"correct_options":["A semi-colon"],"exam_topics":["Success events & the product variable principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following variables is reserved for Tracking Code?","presented_options":["s.campaign","s.products","s.purchaseID","s.evar1"],"correct_options":["s.campaign"],"exam_topics":["Conversion variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following variables is used for custom conversions?","presented_options":["s.transactionID","s.products","s.evar1 - s.evar100","s.purchaseID"],"correct_options":["s.evar1 - s.evar100"],"exam_topics":["Conversion variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"What are the attributes of a good tracking code?","presented_options":["Unique","Upper case","Short","Granular","Generic"],"correct_options":["Unique","Short","Granular"],"exam_topics":["Conversion variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the byte limitation for the campaign and eVar variables?","presented_options":["255 bytes","150 bytes","50 bytes","100 bytes per field"],"correct_options":["255 bytes"],"exam_topics":["Conversion variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following options within Adobe Analytics allow you to group conversions by categories and subcategories?","presented_options":["eVar variables","Marketing channels","Classifications","Campaign variables"],"correct_options":["Classifications"],"exam_topics":["Conversion variables principles"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 6","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following Admin Logs do you use to display changes made to Report Suites outside Admin tools?","presented_options":["Report suite change log","Browser log","Admin tools log","Usage & Access log"],"correct_options":["Report suite change log"],"exam_topics":["Intro to administrative tools of reports and analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"What are the Logs within Admin Tools?","presented_options":["Usage & access log","Report suite change log","Admin tools log","Browser log","Diagnostic log"],"correct_options":["Usage & access log","Report suite change log","Admin tools log"],"exam_topics":["Intro to administrative tools of reports and analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which Report Suite Manager setting provides you a list of common preconfigured settings?","presented_options":["Report suite groups","Report suite templates","Rollup & global report suites","Download settings"],"correct_options":["Report suite templates"],"exam_topics":["Intro to administrative tools of reports and analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"In the General settings for the report suite, which of the following are functions of Custom Menus?","presented_options":["Create new reports","Drag folders or reports to new locations","Create new folders","Create a new dashboard","Rename sections, folders, and reports"],"correct_options":["Drag folders or reports to new locations","Create new folders","Rename sections, folders, and reports"],"exam_topics":["Intro to administrative tools of reports and analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Where in Adobe Analytics can you create a new Publishing List?","presented_options":["Admin tab > user management > publishing list manager","Admin tab > user management > report suites","Admin tab > user management > Email user","Admin tab > user management > Add publishing list"],"correct_options":["Admin tab > user management > publishing list manager"],"exam_topics":["Intro to administrative tools of reports and analytics"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are best practices when using data sources?","presented_options":["Do not use the .fin file","Reserve metric and dimension reports for external data","Practice uploading and verify numbers in a development report suite","Upload large amounts of data in a single file"],"correct_options":["Reserve metric and dimension reports for external data","Practice uploading and verify numbers in a development report suite"],"exam_topics":["Explore data import tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following tools can you use to import data into Reports & Analytics?","presented_options":["Web services API","Data warehouse","Report builder","Data sources"],"correct_options":["Web services API","Data sources"],"exam_topics":["Explore data import tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"When Customer Attributes are enabled, in which Reports & Analytics menu can you find the relevant reports?","presented_options":["Visitor profile","Site metrics","Visitor retention","Custom reports"],"correct_options":["Visitor profile"],"exam_topics":["Explore data import tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How far back can the Classification Rule Builder classify data?","presented_options":["Indefinitely","Three months","One month","Six months"],"correct_options":["Six months"],"exam_topics":["Explore data import tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following can have classified data added to them?","presented_options":["eVars","Geosegmentation","Props","Traffic sources"],"correct_options":["eVars","Props"],"exam_topics":["Explore data import tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How many channels or buckets can a hit in the marketing channels report fall into?","presented_options":["One","Two","Four","Intimate"],"correct_options":["One"],"exam_topics":["Server side data manipulation"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Who must set up the VISTA rules for you?","presented_options":["ClientCare","Adobe consulting","Adobe engineering services","You can set them up yourself"],"correct_options":["Adobe engineering services"],"exam_topics":["Server side data manipulation"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How many conditions can you create for a single processing rule?","presented_options":["1","10","30","Unlimited"],"correct_options":["30"],"exam_topics":["Server side data manipulation"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following rules is processed first?","presented_options":["Marketing channels","Processing rules","VISTA rules","All are independent and processed at the same time"],"correct_options":["Processing rules"],"exam_topics":["Server side data manipulation"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"You set a value for prop3 in the page code, and you set it in the AppMeasurement file using a plug-in. What will happen when the data is processed in Reports & Analytics?","presented_options":["The value set on the page code is reported","The value set in the AppMeasurement file is reported","Both values are reported","Neither value is reported"],"correct_options":["The value set in the AppMeasurement file is reported"],"exam_topics":["Server side data manipulation"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which tool exports data from the processed data in Reports & Analytics?","presented_options":["Data sources","Report builder","Data warehouse","Ad hoc"],"correct_options":["Report builder"],"exam_topics":["Extract data with exporting tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Who has access to Data Workbench?","presented_options":["Analytics standard customers","It's an individual add on project","Users of the data workbench group in user management","Analytics premium customers"],"correct_options":["Analytics premium customers"],"exam_topics":["Extract data with exporting tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"How many data requests (data blocks) can you have in a single Report Builder Excel file?","presented_options":["50","10","Unlimited","100"],"correct_options":["Unlimited"],"exam_topics":["Extract data with exporting tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are benefits of Ad Hoc Analysis?","presented_options":["Unlimited breakdowns","Unlimited metrics per report","Advanced pathing repors","Advanced user management","Unlimited data set size"],"correct_options":["Unlimited breakdowns","Unlimited metrics per report","Advanced pathing reports"],"exam_topics":["Extract data with exporting tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"Which of the following are the benefits of using Data Warehouse?","presented_options":["Unlimited rows of data","No restrictions on breakdowns and metrics","Multiple charts and graphs per data set","Unlimited pathing reports"],"correct_options":["Unlimited rows of data","No restrictions on breakdowns and metrics"],"exam_topics":["Extract data with exporting tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following tools is best for reporting data from multiple report suites in a single report?","presented_options":["Data warehouse","Data sources","Ad hoc","Report builder"],"correct_options":["Report builder"],"exam_topics":["Take action with data management tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which of the following data importing tools do you use to upload offline metrics into Reports and Analytics?","presented_options":["Classifications","Customer attributes","Data sources and connectors","Web services API"],"correct_options":["Data sources and connectors"],"exam_topics":["Take action with data management tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What is the primary purpose of the Dynamic Variables tool?","presented_options":["To capture values from a query string","To estimate website conversions via marketing channels","To divide data by report suites","To shorten the length of image requests"],"correct_options":["To shorten the length of image requests"],"exam_topics":["Take action with data management tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"In which step of the Web Analytics Process do you deliver actionable insights based on the analytics data?","presented_options":["Report","Optimize","Define and measure","Innovate","Analyze"],"correct_options":["Analyze"],"exam_topics":["Take action with data management tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which Data Export tool allows the export of more than a half million rows of data?","presented_options":["Data warehouse and data feeds","Data workbench","Ad hoc","Report builder"],"correct_options":["Data warehouse and data feeds"],"exam_topics":["Take action with data management tools"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 7","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What are the four components that are available in the Analysis Workspace report table?","presented_options":["Data extracts, metrics, targets, time","Dimensions, alerts, targets, report suites","Data extracts, alerts, segments, report suites","Dimensions, metrics, segments, time"],"correct_options":["Dimensions, metrics, segments, time"],"exam_topics":["Intro to reporting using analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What do you call a collection of data that is considered a single site for reporting needs?","presented_options":["Report suite","Classification","Contribution analysis","Freeform table"],"correct_options":["Report suite"],"exam_topics":["Intro to reporting using analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"In which formats can you download Analysis Workspace projects?","presented_options":["CSV","Microsoft word","HTML","PDF"],"correct_options":["CSV","PDF"],"exam_topics":["Intro to reporting using analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"What does a project in Analysis Workspace include?","presented_options":["My recommended reports","Panels","Visualizations","Components","Project links"],"correct_options":["Panels","Visualizations","Components"],"exam_topics":["Intro to reporting using analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Your team have been sending reports using the visit-based segment container. But later decides to send report data using a hit-based container. What will happen to the report after this change?","presented_options":["The page views will decrease","The visitors will decrease","The visits will increase","The page views will increase"],"correct_options":["The page views will decrease"],"exam_topics":["Customization features in analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which Segmentation container is primarily useful for multi-session analysis?","presented_options":["Visit container","Logic group container","Hit container","Visitor container"],"correct_options":["Visitor container"],"exam_topics":["Customization features in analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What do you call a segment applied at the column level?","presented_options":["Cross-tab analysis","Ad hoc column analysis","Multi-dimensional analysis","Internal column analysis"],"correct_options":["Cross-tab analysis"],"exam_topics":["Customization features in analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What does conditional formatting do?","presented_options":["Determines if a cell shows/hides all cell formatting","Formats upper, midpoint, and lower limits on report data","Sets the condition to show a 0 or blank cell","Determines if a cell shows/hides the numeric value for the metric"],"correct_options":["Formats upper, midpoint, and lower limits on report data"],"exam_topics":["Customization features in analysis workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the two correct answers. ","question_text":"What are two Traffic Sources dimensions?","presented_options":["Search engines","Search keywords","Searches","Campaign ID"],"correct_options":["Not search engine, campaign id"],"exam_topics":["Visitor acquisition and identification reporting in workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the three correct answers. ","question_text":"What dimensions do Technology Reports include?","presented_options":["Operating systems","Browser types","Monitor resolutions","Tracking code","Page"],"correct_options":["Operating systems","Browser Types","Monitor resolutions"],"exam_topics":["Visitor acquisition and identification reporting in workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"rWhat does Adobe Analytics use to determine the location of the visitor? ","presented_options":["Cities dimension","Regions dimension","IP address","Tracking code"],"correct_options":["IP address"],"exam_topics":["Visitor acquisition and identification reporting in workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The social marketing team lead would like a report that lists the top social referring domains that drive traffic you your website. Which report would be most effective?","presented_options":["Referrer type broken down by referring domains","Referrers broken down by referrer type","Referrers broken down by social domains","Original referrer type broken down by social domains"],"correct_options":["Referrer type broken down by referring domains"],"exam_topics":["Visitor acquisition and identification reporting in workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"Which report gives you in-depth insight into how visitors get to your website? ","presented_options":["Traffic source report","Media report","Campaign report","Technology report"],"correct_options":["Campaign report"],"exam_topics":["Visitor acquisition and identification reporting in workspace"],"question_source":"Adobe Test - Step 8","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"What method would prevent duplicate products from being reported when a visitor refreshes their page during the checkout process?","presented_options":["Classifications","Event Serialization","Merchandising","PurchaseID"],"correct_options":["PurchaseID"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The Chief Marketing Officer (CMO) notices a sudden drop in the conversion rate between the product detail pages and order confirmation page. The analyst needs to investigate the cause of the drop. Which type of report should the analyst use?","presented_options":["Pathing","Orders","Last touch marketing channel","Most popular pages"],"correct_options":["Pathing"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"An analyst needs the most efficient method to directly import, create, and maintain a dashboard in Microsoft Excel. Which tool in the Adobe Analytics suite should the analyst use?","presented_options":["Excel client","Workspace","Report builder","Data warehouse"],"correct_options":["Report builder"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"An analyst needs to provide weekly data in CSV format that will provide multiple eVars, props, and metrics without limitations on the depth of the data. Which Adobe Analytics tool should the analyst use?","presented_options":["Data warehouse","Report builder","Workspace","Ad hoc analysis"],"correct_options":["Data warehouse"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"An analyst is sharing a dashboard with other users. A user has stated that they do NOT see the dashboard. What should the user do to access the dashboard?","presented_options":["The user should look in the \"Dashboards\" folder in the Reports menu to find the dashboard as soon as it was shared.","The user should respond \"Yes\" to the shared dashboard prompt when next logging in to add view the dashboard.","The user should select the “copy me” or “on menu” options next to the shared dashboard in the Dashboard Manager","The user should click through the notification email they received in order to access the shared dashboard."],"correct_options":["The user should select the “copy me” or “on menu” options next to the shared dashboard in the Dashboard Manager"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"A business must be alerted if more than $5,000 of revenue is recorded during any single hour of the day. During the 2 PM hour, the business receives revenue of $7,500. When will Adobe Analytics send this alert?","presented_options":["As soon as more than $5,000 in revenue is recorded in any rolling 60-minute period","As soon as more than $5,000 in revenue is recorded in a standard hour (i.e., 2-3 PM)","At the end of the hour where more than $5,000 in revenue was recorded","At the end of the day for each hour where $5,000 in revenue was exceeded"],"correct_options":["At the end of the hour where more than $5,000 in revenue was recorded"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"An analyst creates a new segment that needs to be shared with other Adobe Analytics users within the organization. After creating and selecting the segment in the Segment Manager, the analyst then clicks Approve. Adobe Analytics users indicate that they are unable to choose the segment for reporting. Why are the Adobe Analytics users unable to use this segment in reporting?","presented_options":["The segment was never shared with the users","The users need to create their own versions of the segment","The users need to copy the segment to their account.","The segment was not tagged in the Segment Manager."],"correct_options":["The segment was never shared with the users"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"An analyst needs to review the most popular pages report with the visits metrics for first-time visits from mobile devices. Two segments currently exist in Adobe Analytics that may be helpful: 1. First Time Visits (visits where visit number -1) 2. Mobile Visits (visits where Mobile Device exists) What should the analyst do to segment the pages report for first-time visits from mobile devices?","presented_options":["Use segment stacking to apply both segments to the pages report","Use the Segment Editor to apply both segments to the pages report","Use the Segment Manager to apply both segments to the pages report","Use the admin console to apply both segments to the pages report"],"correct_options":["Use segment stacking to apply both segments to the pages report"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"An analyst needs to classify incoming campaign tracking codes for the affiliate marketing channel. Traffic from the affiliate marketing channel sets a tracking code value such as: > aff_campaign-site_campaign-link-id The “campaign-site” and “campaign-link-id” values are set by multiple channels and can have values that are at the discretion of the marketing department. The “aff” prefix is a constant value that identifies the Affiliate marketing channel. Traffic from the Affiliate marketing channel must be classified as “Affiliate” in the Marketing Channel Name classification report. How should the analyst configure this classification rule?","presented_options":["Tracking code starts with “aff_”","Tracking code contains “affiliate”","Tracking code ends with “aff”","Tracking code contains “aff”"],"correct_options":["Tracking code starts with “aff_”"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"An analyst needs to report on campaign performance size, location, brand, and spend. The campaign was created as www.xyzsite.com/home.html?cid=123 and has been live for 2 weeks. How should the analyst report on the required campaign attributes?","presented_options":["Create a segment for size, location, brand and spend","Run the campaign report with revenue as the metric","Run the “tracking code” report with visits as the metric","Add classifications for size, location, brand, and spend"],"correct_options":["Add classifications for size, location, brand, and spend"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }, 
      {
      "question_type":"Select the correct answer. ","question_text":"The analyst needs to create a reporting environment for Adobe Analytics. Users must quickly be able to see all reports for only visits in which a visitor used a mobile device. There is currently no separate Adobe Analytics report suite for this mobile traffic. What should the analyst do?","presented_options":["Create a “Mobile Visits” view of the main report suite from within the report suite settings","Create a Virtual Report Suite using the “Mobile Visits” segment","Create a new User Group and lock the segment “Mobile Visits” to that user group","Create a processing rule in report suite settings that moves all mobile visits into a new report suite"],"correct_options":["Create a Virtual Report Suite using the “Mobile Visits” segment"],"exam_topics":[],"question_source":"Practice Exam Questions","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
      }
      
  ]
}